Dinosaur Hunter
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
I'm home!
What's this? A Dinosaur?
Quietly...
It was not a dream.
I did saw it after all.
How weird!
Where'd it go?
That was interesting!
Doraemon, there was a super giant dinosaur here just now!
Did you see it?
Oh, you saw it?
Actually, I'm went dinosaur hunting with Sewashi-kun.
Dinosaur hunting?
It's an super-interesting sports that's trending now in the 22nd century.
Oh! So, that dinosaur was...?!
Yes, Sewashi-kun was taking it to 22nd century....
from 10,000,000,000 years ago using time machine.
He decided to give it a rest here for a while.
So that Sewashi-kun can have a dinosaur as a pet.
Sounds fun!
All right, I'm going to join you guys!
Wait, Nobita-kun!
What was that for? You're so mean, Doraemon!
It's a very dangerous sport.
You have to have strong body and be consistent.
also the guts to be not scared of anything.
For me, it's not a problem.
But Nobita-kun, do you have those qualities?
Well....
Ah! There's a rat!
~Kyaa! I'm afraid of rats!
I am so scared!
I HATE rats!
Actually I lied!
You are brave, huh?  You sure don't say....
Strong body and youth, huh?
OK, I will take you with me!
You wanna join us, right?
But you have to be prepared before you hunt dinosaurs.
Go get butter and jam.
Sure!
That's too much, I told you to bring only butter and jelly.
Why not, these are for our lunch.
Alright, we're ready now!
Let's dash off to hunt Dinosaurs!
Ouch!
So this is the world, 10,000,000,000 years ago, it's so cool! Yay!
But Doraemon, tell me! How are we going to hunt Dinosaurs?
Count on me, I have my secret weapon.
Cell Atrophy Gun!
No matter how big some biological being is, it will shrink only in a seconds.
Huh, I got the wrong one.
It's this one!
Wrong one!
This!
It's all this messy because you put unnecessary stuff in my pocket!
I got it!
Let me show you how powerful this machine is.
How cool! It shrunk and became so small!
Let me try!
Nobita-kun, it's hard to control, y'know.
Don't try to use it randomly, when there's no dinosaur around!
All right!
OK, let me go lure them.
I feel very scared, I think we'd better go home.
Nobita-kun, here comes the big one!
Nobita-kun, shoot him, hurry up!
Don't run, Nobita! You must shoot, now!
Nobita-kun, stop, it's enough.
See, it's like an ant now, you can't make it bigger now.
Sorry, dino.
I will do it.
Now butter and jam...
Are we gonna eat now?
Wrong, you see....
How mean! You have gone too far, Doraemon!
To think that you'd use me as a bait to lure the dinosaur...
...with butter and jelly on my face and head.
Doraemon, found one!
See, Doraemon!
I am experienced, so I am not nervous at all.
See how calm I am!
What are you doing, Doraemon? Shoot it!
I'm not scared, unlike you.
I understand, so hurry up!
Take it out!
Well? I got the wrong one...
Hurry up!
Not this, not this!
I have got it!
Help!
Please help!
Don't eat us!
It's terrible, we're so scared!
Let's run now!
B-but my glasses!
No time for that!
Dinosaur fossil discovered with eyeglasses
from 10,000,000,000 years ago.
It's a big news even in the parliament right now.
Big news!